<?xml version="1.0"?>
<factOrCrap>
    <card>
        <question>Readers Digest is the most widely read publication in the world.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>Elvis did a TV ad for a donut.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>Celine Dion was named for a Canadian Prime Minister.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>The word paparazzi literally means crazy fly.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>NASA beamed a Beatles song to Polaris.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>The old jail cell of Nelson Mandela is now a tourist attraction.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>The US Marines were founded in a Philadelphia tavern</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>Music was initially used to soothe riders who were afraid of falling.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>Recycling one glass jar saves enough energy to watch TV for 3 hours.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>Your body kills 17 million red blood cells per minute.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>The electric chair was invented by a dentist.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
    <question>Cows are one of the main contributors to the hole in the ozone layer.</question>
    <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>An espresso has less caffeine than a cup of coffee.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>Clint Eastwood wrote many of the scores for his movies.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>J.M. Barrie, author of Peter Pan was only five feet tall.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>Humans shed about 600,000 particles of skin every hour.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>    
    <card>
        <question>A total eclipse of the sun happens once every 11 years.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>Venus is the second planet from the sun.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>There is a city called Rome on every continent.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>    
    <card>
        <question>Black olives are grown in warmer cliemates then thier green cousins.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>There was no actual, rock, at Plymouth.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>Tofurky is a city in the Turtle Islands.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>   
    <card>
        <question>Jackie Robinson played himself in his film bio.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>   
    <card>
        <question>Rhinoceros beetles are on of the strongest animals on the planet.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>   
    <card>
        <question> Louisiana, stems from the French work for, boot.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>   
    <card>
        <question>The Pioneer was the first spacecraft to orbit Uranus.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>   
    <card>
        <question>Narcolepsy is a fear of drugs.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>   
    <card>
        <question>Two, nibbles, make a byte in computer terminology.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>
    <card>
        <question>The heart beat rate of a cat is twice that of humans.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>     
    <card>
        <question>A, burn card, in poker is the low end of a straight.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>             
    <card>
        <question>Honey is the only food that does not have a shelf life.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>                     
    <card>
        <question>Trench coats were used, quite literally, in the trenches.</question>
        <answer>Fact</answer>
    </card>                                     
    <card>
        <question>The word Arkansas mean, sturdy boat.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card> 
    <card>
        <question>The world's largest silver nugget was found in Minnesota.</question>
        <answer>Crap</answer>
    </card>                     
</factOrCrap>














